#### Contact

Adrija Apartment, 196/A, Kalicharan Ghosh Road, Kolkata Landmark: Niyogi Jewellers PIN: 700050 8777831265 (Mobile) imakeothersmile@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/thisisaditi (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

**Version Control** 

Git

GitHub

### Languages

Hindi (Elementary)
English (Full Professional)
Bengali (Full Professional)

### Certifications

Create a no-code responsive website with Webflow

IBM Cybersecurity Analyst Specialization

Programming with JavaScript Build an App with Adalo

Core Java

# Aditi Ray

| Frontend Developer #| Web Designer | Graphic Designer || Virtualizing Dreams to Reality! 

▼

Kolkata, West Bengal, India

## Summary

I am a freelance Web Designer, Web Developer, App Developer as well as a Graphic designer with nearly 2 years of experience along with professional certifications. I am a happy desktop always eager to learn new skills and explore them in a best possible way.

### Key Skills:

- Programming Languages: Core JAVA, HTML, JavaScript, PHP and CSS
- Database Design: MySQL
- · No Code Development: Webflow, Figma, Adalo, Canva
- Operating Systems: Windows, Linux
- Web Development, Front End Development, Android Development
- Graphic Design: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, InDesign, CorelDraw

You can check out my work at: aditiray.dorik.io Check out My GitHub: https://github.com/iamaditiray

I adept at collaborating with dynamic teams to build high quality websites and identify opportunities to enhance the user experience. Need someone who will care about your success, communicate clearly, and anticipate options that minimize unwanted surprises? I want to be that person for you. Let's get started!

# Experience

Freelance

Web Designer

February 2021 - Present (2 years 2 months)

I am a Web developer, Web Dessigner and Graphic Designer specialising in high-quality Full-Stack Development and UI-UX designing.

Need someone who will care about your success, communicate clearly, and anticipate options that minimize unwanted surprises? I want to be that person for you. Let's get started!

DREAMS CLUES®#
Graphic Designer
June 2022 - August 2022 (3 months)

Kolkata, West Bengal, India

I have worked as a Graphic Designing Intern at Dreams' Clues for 2 months. I have applied for this post via Internshala. It was a very skillful as well conquering experience as I was introduced towards the industry requirements and also privileged to work on several diligent team projects along with the individual ones.

Chamela Helpdia Charitable Trust (CHCT)
Graphic Designer
May 2022 - June 2022 (2 months)
Kolkata, West Bengal, India

I have worked as a Designing Intern in Chamela Helpdia Charitable Trust for 1 month. I have applied for this post via Internshala. I was honored and privileged to be selected as their intern and so glad for having the opportunity to work with their well organized team. I came across a lot of experienced coworkers who helped me throughout in my growth during the internship period.

## Education

University of Engineering & Management (UEM)

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Software Engineering · (March 2020 - March 2024)

Holy Child Institute Girls' Higher Secondary School Higher Secondary Education, Computer Science (2018 - 2020)